Guide to the Duke University Living History Program records, 1973-2005 and undated UA.22.02.0001
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Interviews, 1973-2005 and undated; 1
  - Mihai, King Michael of Romania, 1991 February 11; 41
    - Original VHS Video-cassette, 1991 February 11 (Box 5, Video-cassette UA.22.02.0001-VHS-0035)
      Duke University Living History Program Presents A Conversation with King Mihai of Romania; February 11, 1991; Use Copy; Tape Two; Part One 59:30; Part Two 60:00
    - Original VHS Video-cassette, 1991 February 11 (Box 5, Video-cassette UA.22.02.0001-VHS-0036)
      Duke University Living History Program Presents A Conversation with King Mihai of Romania; February 11, 1991; Tape One; Part One 57:00; Part Two 58:30
    - Original VHS Video-cassette, 1991 February 11 (Box 5, Video-cassette UA.22.02.0001-VHS-0037)
      Duke University Living History Program Presents A Conversation with King Mihai of Romania; February 11, 1991; Tape Two; Part One 59:30; Part wo-60:00
    - Transcript (3 copies), undated (Box 26)
    - Transcript (3 copies), undated (Box 27)
  - Misinformation in Crisis Management: the Vietnam War, 1990-1991; 42
    - Original 1/4-inch Audio-reel, 1990 March 2 (Audio-reel UA.22.02.0001-RR-0001)
      Living History; Misinformation; 3/2/90; 15 IPS; Dolby A; Dolby Tone at Head; Room Tone at Tail
    - Original 3/4-inch Video-cassette, 1990 March 2 (Box 14, Video-cassette UA.22.02.0001-Umatic-0116)
      Living History; "Misinformation"; Lomperis Framing Commentary; Tape 1; 3-2-90; with TC
    - Original 3/4-inch Video-cassette, 1990 March 2 (Box 14, Video-cassette UA.22.02.0001-Umatic-0117)
      Living History; "Misinformation"; Lomperis Framing Commentary; Tape 2; 3-2-90; with TC
    - Original betacam-sp Video-cassette, 1991 January (Box 10, Video-cassette UA.22.02.0001-Bcam-0043)
      Misinformation in Crisis Management: The Vietnam War; Duke Living History Program; Assembled Jan. 1991; 36:28; Edited Master
    - Transcript, undated (Box 27)
  - Mohammed, Deen Imam, 1992 April 16; 43
    - Original betacam-sp Video-cassette, 1992 April 16 (Box 9, Video-cassette UA.22.02.0001-Bcam-0033)
      Living History Interview; Imam Deen Mohammed; w/ C. Eric Lincoln; V. Cornell; B. Lawrence; 4-16-92; Segment One 62:00; Segment two: 25:45; Master
    - Original VHS Video-cassette, 1992 April 16 (Box 16, Video-cassette UA.22.02.0001-VHS-0042)
      Duke University Living History Program Presents A Conversation with Imam Deen Mohammed; Muslim American Spokesman; April 16, 1992; Part One-62:00; Part Two-25:45
    - Original VHS Video-cassette, 1992 April 16 (Box 16, Video-cassette UA.22.02.0001-VHS-0043)
      Duke University Living History Program Presents A Conversation with Imam Deen Mohammed; Muslim American Spokesman; April 16, 1992; Part One-62:00; Part Two-25:45 Use Copy
    - Transcript (2 copies), 1992 (Box 27)
  - Nakasone, Yasuhiro, 1990 September 17; 44
    - Original VHS Video-cassette, 1990 September 17 (Box 5, Video-cassette UA.22.02.0001-VHS-0008)
      The Duke University Living History Program presents; A Conversation with Yasuhiro Nakasone; former Prime Minister of Japan; September 17, 1990; Part one - 61:00; part two - 38:30
    - Original VHS Video-cassette, 1990 September 17 (Box 5, Video-cassette UA.22.02.0001-VHS-0009)
    - Original betacam-sp Video-cassette, 1990 September 17 (Box 10, Video-cassette UA.22.02.0001-Bcam-0035)
      Nak; Hour 1; Program; 61:00; 1 Nak; 2 Ambruce; 3 Panel; 4 Interp; 9-17-90
    - Original betacam-sp Video-cassette, 1990 September 17 (Box 10, Video-cassette UA.22.02.0001-Bcam-0036)
      Nak; Hour 2; Prog; 38:30 program time with credits; 1 Nak; 2 Ambruce; 3 Panel; 4 Interp; Includes insert returns at close; 9-17-90
    - Original betacam-sp Video-cassette, 1990 September 17 (Box 10, Video-cassette UA.22.02.0001-Bcam-0037)
      Nak; Hour 1; ISO; 1 Nak; 2 Ambruce; 3 Panel; 4 Interp; 9-17-90
    - Original betacam-sp Video-cassette, 1990 September 17 (Box 10, Video-cassette UA.22.02.0001-Bcam-0038)
      Nak; Hour 2; ISO; 1 Nak; 2 Ambruce; 3 Panel; 4 Interp; 9-17-90
    - Transcript (3 copies), undated (Box 27)
  - Nitze, Paul, 1989 and undated; 45
    - Original 3/4-inch Video-cassette, undated (Box 8, Video-cassette UA.22.02.0001-Umatic-0057)
      Nitze 1
    - Original 3/4-inch Video-cassette, undated (Box 8, Video-cassette UA.22.02.0001-Umatic-0058)
      Nitze 2
    - Original 3/4-inch Video-cassette, 1989 October 10 (Box 8, Video-cassette UA.22.02.0001-Umatic-0059)
      Paul Nitze Lecture; 10-10-89; Gross Chem
    - Original 3/4-inch Video-cassette, 1989 October 11 (Box 8, Video-cassette UA.22.02.0001-Umatic-0060)
      Living History; 10-11-89 - Nitze; ISO - Cam 1
    - Original 3/4-inch Video-cassette, 1989 October 11 (Box 8, Video-cassette UA.22.02.0001-Umatic-0061)
    - Transcript (4 copies), undated (Box 27)
      see also Cuban Missle Crisis
  - Ozal, Turgut, 1991 March 26; 46
    - Original betacam-sp Video-cassette, 1991 March 26 (Box 9, Video-cassette UA.22.02.0001-Bcam-0034)
      3-26-91; Run time 1 hour 21 minutes (with credits); Living History; Ozal; Program; 1 + 3 Ozal; 2 + 4 Panel
    - Original VHS Video-cassette, 1991 March 26 (Box 5, Video-cassette UA.22.02.0001-VHS-0010)
      The Duke University Living History Program presents; A Conversation with Turgut Ozal; President of Turkey; March 26, 1991; 1:21:00
    - Original VHS Video-cassette, 1991 March 26 (Box 5, Video-cassette UA.22.02.0001-VHS-0011)
    - Transcript, undated (Box 27)
  - Percy, Charles H., 1986 August 19; 47
    - Original Video-cassette, 1986 August 19 (Box 19, Video-cassette UA.22.02.0001-Umatic-0157)
      Duke University Living History Program; Senator Charles H. Percy; 1985/86 rutherfurd Lecturer; Interviewed by: Drs. Bruce Kuniholm & Alex Roland; Filmed In: Rare Book Room, Perkins Library; audio: mono 2-track; video: 16 minutes; duplicate of tape 3; contents: personal relations with soviets; mms 8-19-86
    - Original Video-cassette, 1986 August 19 (Box 19, Video-cassette UA.22.02.0001-Umatic-0158)
      Duke University Living History Program; Senator Charles H. Percy; 1985/86 rutherfurd Lecturer; Interviewed by: Dr. Ole Holsti; Filmed In: Rare Book Room, Perkins Library; audio: mono 2-track; video: 57 minutes; duplicate of tape 4; contents: VietNam involvement, Role of american Military ini third world conflicts, Central America and our Security interest, War Powers Act, Bipartisanship in domestic economic sphere and in international arms control; mms 8-19-86
    - Original Video-cassette, 1986 August 19 (Box 20, Video-cassette UA.22.02.0001-Umatic-0159)
      Duke University Living History Program; Senator Charles H. Percy; 1985/86 rutherfurd Lecturer; Interviewed by: Dr. James Barber; Filmed In: Rare Book Room, Perkins Library; audio: mono 2-track; video: 58 minutes; duplicate of tape 5; contents: Arms control, Percy's personal background including his religious upbringing and his formal education; mms 8-19-86
    - Original Video-cassette, 1986 August 19 (Box 20, Video-cassette UA.22.02.0001-Umatic-0160)
      Duke University Living History Program; Senator Charles H. Percy; 1985/86 rutherfurd Lecturer; Interviewed by: Dr. Ralph Braibanti; Filmed In: Rare Book Room, Perkins Library; audio: mono 2-track; video: 31 minutes; duplicate of tape 6; contents: third world relations; mms 8-19-86
    - Original Video-cassette, 1986 August 19 (Box 20, Video-cassette UA.22.02.0001-Umatic-0161)
      Duke University Living History Program; Senator Charles H. Percy; 1985/86 rutherfurd Lecturer; Filmed In: The Film Theatre of the Bryan Center audio: mono 2-track; video: 61 minutes; duplicate of tape 6; contents: percy addresses students about improving United States position in world economy; mms 8-19-86
    - Original 3/4-inch Video-cassette, 1986 August 19 (Box 8, Video-cassette UA.22.02.0001-Umatic-0062)
      Duke University Living History Program; Senator charles H. Percy -- 1985/86 Rutherfurd Lecturer; Interviewers: Drs. Bruce Kuniholm, Alex Roland; Tape 1; Edited Master
    - Original 3/4-inch Video-cassette, 1986 August 19 (Box 8, Video-cassette UA.22.02.0001-Umatic-0063)
      Duke University Living History Program; Senator charles H. Percy -- 1985/86 Rutherfurd Lecturer; Interviewers: Drs. Bruce Kuniholm, Alex Roland; Tape 2; Edited Master
    - Original 3/4-inch Video-cassette, 1986 August 19 (Box 8, Video-cassette UA.22.02.0001-Umatic-0064)
      Duke University Living History Program; Senator charles H. Percy -- 1985/86 Rutherfurd Lecturer; Interviewers: Drs. Bruce Kuniholm, Alex Roland; Tape 3; Edited Master
    - Original 3/4-inch Video-cassette, 1986 August 19 (Box 8, Video-cassette UA.22.02.0001-Umatic-0065)
      Duke University Living History Program; Senator charles H. Percy -- 1985/86 Rutherfurd Lecturer; Interviewers: Dr. Ole Holsti; Tape 4; Edited Master
    - Original 3/4-inch Video-cassette, 1986 August 19 (Box 8, Video-cassette UA.22.02.0001-Umatic-0066)
      Duke University Living History Program; Senator charles H. Percy -- 1985/86 Rutherfurd Lecturer; Interviewers: Dr. James D. Barber; Tape 5; Edited Master
    - Original 3/4-inch Video-cassette, 1986 August 19 (Box 8, Video-cassette UA.22.02.0001-Umatic-0067)
      Duke University Living History Program; Senator charles H. Percy -- 1985/86 Rutherfurd Lecturer; Interviewers: Dr. Ralph Braibanti; Tape 6; Edited Master
    - Original 3/4-inch Video-cassette, 1986 August 19 (Box 15, Video-cassette UA.22.02.0001-Umatic-0126)
      Duke Unviersity Living History Program; Senator charles H. Percy -- 1985/86; rutherfurd Lecturer; Interviewed by: Drs. Bruce Kuniholm and Alex Roland; filmed in: Rare Book Room, Perkins Library; audio: mono 2-track; video: 48 minutes; 15 secs. Bars & 1 khz tone; Duplicate; Tape 1; contents: background in foreign relations and current professional goals; mms 8-19-86
    - Original 3/4-inch Video-cassette, 1986 August 19 (Box 15, Video-cassette UA.22.02.0001-Umatic-0127)
      Duke Unviersity Living History Program; Senator charles H. Percy -- 1985/86; rutherfurd Lecturer; Interviewed by: Drs. Bruce Kuniholm and Alex Roland; filmed in: Rare Book Room, Perkins Library; audio: mono 2-track; video: 47 minutes; 15 secs. Bars & 1 khz tone; Duplicate; Tape 2; contents: Military Industrial Complex, Leadership in senate and white house, assessment, impressions of foreign leaders; mms 8-19-86
    - Transcript (4 copies), 1985 (Box 27)
      see also Israel/AIPAC Lobby
  - Reagan, Ronald, 1988 February 8; 48
    - Original 3/4-inch Video-cassette, 1988 February 8 (Box 11, Video-cassette UA.22.02.0001-Umatic-0068)
      Ronald Reagan at Duke University; 2/8/88; Edit Master; Audio: 1 and 2; TC on TC track
    - Original 3/4-inch Video-cassette, 1988 February 8 (Box 11, Video-cassette UA.22.02.0001-Umatic-0069)
      Ronald Reagan at Duke University; Febrary 8, 1988; Tape #2: Forum on drug abuse in the workplace, preliminary to Reagan's entrance; audio; tracks 1 and 2 / no TC; camera original
    - Original 3/4-inch Video-cassette, 1988 February 8 (Box 11, Video-cassette UA.22.02.0001-Umatic-0070)
      Ronald Reagan at Duke University; February 8, 1988; Tape #3: RR's entrance; participation in forum; speech; exit; audio: tracks 1 and 2 / No TC; camera original
    - Original 3/4-inch Video-cassette, 1988 February 8 (Box 11, Video-cassette UA.22.02.0001-Umatic-0071)
      The trip of the president to Duke University; February 8, 1988; Tape #1: Cutaways/crowd shots; audio: tracks 1 and 2 TC on TC track; Cameron Indoor Stadium
    - Original 3/4-inch Video-cassette, undated (Box 15, Video-cassette UA.22.02.0001-Umatic-0125)
      Ronald Reagan Dub 3/4"
  - Rhine, J.B., November 1973; 49
    - Original 3/4-inch Video-cassette, November 1973 (Box 11, Video-cassette UA.22.02.0001-Umatic-0072)
      Dr. J.B. Rhine Interview at Duke; November 1973; for the Rutherfurd collection; Perkins Library; This tape begins with an introduction by Jay Rutherfurd about the establishment of the Rutherfurd Audiovisual program at Duke. Accompanying Rutherfurd's remarks are exterior views of the Chapel and Perkins Library.
  - Rhine, J. B.; Cooper, John Sherman, undated; 50
    - Original 3/4-inch Video-cassette, undated (Box 15, Video-cassette UA.22.02.0001-Umatic-0124)
      Duke University; Rutherford Collection; 22 minutes; Introduced by J. Rutherford; Rhine/Cooper: Excerpts
    - Original 3/4-inch Video-cassette, undated (Box 11, Video-cassette UA.22.02.0001-Umatic-0073)
      Duke University; rutherford Collection (later living History Coll.); 22 minutes; Introduction by Jay Rutherfurd. Excerpts from interviews with J.B. Rhine and John Sherman Cooper; Master copy?
  - Ross, Dennis, 2005 February 17; 51
    - Original betacam-sp Video-cassette, 2005 February 17 (Box 22, Video-cassette UA.22.02.001-Bcam-0068)
      The Duke Living History program presents A Conversation with Ambassador Dennis Ross; hosted by Bruce Kuniholm; Sanford Center for Public Policy; Master
    - Original betacam-sp Video-cassette, 2005 February 17 (Box 22, Video-cassette UA.22.02.001-Bcam-0069)
      The Duke Living History program presents A Conversation with Ambassador Dennis Ross; hosted by Bruce Kuniholm; Sanford Center for Public Policy; Back-up Master; Contains a few vid hits; Note: False Start with re-take
    - Original VHS Video-cassette, 2005 February 17 (Box 17, Video-cassette UA.22.02.0001-VHS-0103)
      The Duke Living History program presents A Conversation with Ambassador Dennis Ross; hosted by Bruce Kuniholm; Sanford Center for Public Policy; viewing copy 1
    - Original VHS Video-cassette, 2005 February 17 (Box 17, Video-cassette UA.22.02.0001-VHS-0104)
      The Duke Living History program presents A Conversation with Ambassador Dennis Ross; hosted by Bruce Kuniholm; Sanford Center for Public Policy; viewing copy 2
  - Rusk, Dean, 1981; 52
    - Original 1-inch Video-reel, 1981 March 26 (Video-reel UA.22.02.0001-Vid1-0005)
      MRA; Duke University; Dean Rusk Interview; 3-26-81; Reel 1
    - Original 1-inch Video-reel, 1981 March 26 (Video-reel UA.22.02.0001-Vid1-0006)
    - Original 1-inch Video-reel, 1981 March 26 (Video-reel UA.22.02.0001-Vid1-0007)
      MRA; Duke University; Exteriors; 3-26-81
    - Original 3/4-inch Video-cassette, 1981 March 27 (Box 12, Video-cassette UA.22.02.0001-Umatic-0082)
      Duke University; Dean Rusk Faculty Interviews; 3-27-81; Reel #2; with visual time code
    - Original 3/4-inch Video-cassette, 1981 March 27 (Box 12, Video-cassette UA.22.02.0001-Umatic-0083)
      Duke University; Dean Rusk Faculty Interviews; 3-27-81; Reel #3; with visual time code
    - Original 3/4-inch Video-cassette, 1981 March 27 (Box 12, Video-cassette UA.22.02.0001-Umatic-0084)
      Duke University; Dean Rusk Faculty Interviews; 3-27-81; Reel #4; with visual time code
    - Original 3/4-inch Video-cassette, 1981 March 27 (Box 11, Video-cassette UA.22.02.0001-Umatic-0074)
      MRA; Duke University; Dean Rusic Faculty Interviews; 3-27-81; Reel 1; Re-recorded 4-9-81
    - Original 3/4-inch Video-cassette, 1981 March 27 (Box 11, Video-cassette UA.22.02.0001-Umatic-0075)
      MRA; Duke University; Dean Rusk Faculty Interviews; 3-27-81; Reel 2; Re-recorded 4-9-81; Master
    - Original 3/4-inch Video-cassette, 1981 March 27 (Box 11, Video-cassette UA.22.02.0001-Umatic-0076)
      MRA; Duke University; Dean Rusk Faculty Interviews; 3-27-81; Reel 3; Re-recorded 4-9-81
    - Original 3/4-inch Video-cassette, 1981 March 27 (Box 11, Video-cassette UA.22.02.0001-Umatic-0077)
      MRA; Duke University; Dean Rusk Faculty Interviews; 3-27-81; Reel 4; Re-recorded 4-9-81; Master
    - Original 3/4-inch Video-cassette, 1981 March 26 (Box 11, Video-cassette UA.22.02.0001-Umatic-0078)
      MRA; Duke University; Dean Rusk Interview; Cutaways and exterior; 3-26-81
    - Original 3/4-inch Video-cassette, 1981 March 27 (Box 11, Video-cassette UA.22.02.0001-Umatic-0079)
      MRA; Duke University; Dean Rusk Faculty Interviews; 3-27-81; Reel 1
    - Original audiocassette Audio-cassette, 1981 March 26 (Box 23, Audio-cassette UA.22.02.0001-CS-0004)
      Side 1: Pundit Rusk; Jay Rutherfurd Speech; March 26, 1981; Duke University; Side 2: Blank
    - Transcript (3 copies), 1981 (Box 27)
      see also Cuban Missile Crisis and Vietnam: 3 Perspectives
  - Salam, Abdus, 1989 and undated; 53
    - Original 3/4-inch Video-cassette, 1989 January 24 (Box 11, Video-cassette UA.22.02.0001-Umatic-0080)
      Guest: Abdus Salam; Panelists: Ralph Braibanti; Lawrence Evans, Louis Dupree; director: Eric Leary; Length: 54:54; reel 1/2
    - Original 3/4-inch Video-cassette, 1989 January 24 (Box 11, Video-cassette UA.22.02.0001-Umatic-0081)
      Guest: Abdus Salam; Panelists: Ralph Braibanti; Lawrence Evans, Louis Dupree; director: Eric Leary; Length: 55:49; reel 2/2
    - Original dvd, 1989 January 24 (Box 23, Video-disc UA.22.02.0001-DVD-0002)
      Interview with Abdus Salam; January 24, 1989; Master DVD Copy; 5/06
    - Original VHS Video-cassette, 1989 January 24 (Box 5, Video-cassette UA.22.02.0001-VHS-0012)
      The Living History program of duke University presents an interview with Abdus Salam; 1/24/89; VHS duplicate
    - Original VHS Video-cassette, 1989 January 24 (Box 5, Video-cassette UA.22.02.0001-VHS-0013)
    - Original VHS Video-cassette, undated (Box 17, Video-cassette UA.22.02.0001-VHS-0083)
      Program Tape #1; Living History
    - Transcript, undated (Box 27)
  - Sanford, Terry, 1995 January 24; 54
    - Original betacam-sp Video-cassette, 1995 January 24 (Box 10, Video-cassette UA.22.02.0001-Bcam-0039)
      Terry Sanford #1; Living History; 1/24/95; Audio 1 = Terry; Audio 2 = Panel
    - Original betacam-sp Video-cassette, 1995 January 24 (Box 10, Video-cassette UA.22.02.0001-Bcam-0040)
      Terry Sanford; Living History; 1/24/95; Tape 2; Audio/ 2 ch.
    - Transcript, undated (Box 27)
  - Sasakawa, Ryoichi, undated; 55
    - Original 3/4-inch Video-cassette, undated (Box 12, Video-cassette UA.22.02.0001-Umatic-0085)
      2 duke - 1; Campus Scenes; Beauty Shots (continued on roll 2); Master
    - Original 3/4-inch Video-cassette, undated (Box 12, Video-cassette UA.22.02.0001-Umatic-0086)
      2 Duke - 2; Sasakawa arrives; statue; East Campus; Chapel int./ ext.; Master
    - Original 3/4-inch Video-cassette, undated (Box 12, Video-cassette UA.22.02.0001-Umatic-0087)
      2 Duke 3; Sasakawa intv; Master
    - Original 3/4-inch Video-cassette, undated (Box 12, Video-cassette UA.22.02.0001-Umatic-0088)
      2 Duke 4; Sasakawa Intv; Master
    - Original 3/4-inch Video-cassette, undated (Box 12, Video-cassette UA.22.02.0001-Umatic-0089)
      2 Duke 5; Sasakawa Intv; Master
    - Original 3/4-inch Video-cassette, undated (Box 12, Video-cassette UA.22.02.0001-Umatic-0090)
      2 Duke 6; Sasakawa Intv; Master
    - Original 3/4-inch Video-cassette, undated (Box 12, Video-cassette UA.22.02.0001-Umatic-0091)
      2 Duke 7; Sasakawa Intv.; Master
    - Original 3/4-inch Video-cassette, undated (Box 12, Video-cassette UA.22.02.0001-Umatic-0092)
      2 Duke 8; Sasakawa Intv.; plus Duke Opening with music; plus Sasakawa Opening; Master
    - Original 3/4-inch Video-cassette, undated (Box 15, Video-cassette UA.22.02.0001-Umatic-0132)
      2 Duke -1: Campus Scenes
    - Original 3/4-inch Video-cassette, undated (Box 15, Video-cassette UA.22.02.0001-Umatic-0133)
      2 Duke 2: Sasakawa arrives; statue; east campus, chapel int.
    - Original 3/4-inch Video-cassette, undated (Box 15, Video-cassette UA.22.02.0001-Umatic-0134)
      2 Duke 3 - Sasakawa
    - Original 3/4-inch Video-cassette, undated (Box 15, Video-cassette UA.22.02.0001-Umatic-0135)
      2 Duke 4 - Sasakawa Intr
    - Original 3/4-inch Video-cassette, undated (Box 15, Video-cassette UA.22.02.0001-Umatic-0136)
      2 Duke 5 - Sasakawa Intr.
    - Original 3/4-inch Video-cassette, undated (Box 15, Video-cassette UA.22.02.0001-Umatic-0137)
      2 Duke 6 - Sasakawa Intr.
    - Original 3/4-inch Video-cassette, undated (Box 15, Video-cassette UA.22.02.0001-Umatic-0138)
      2 Duke 7 - Sasakawa Intr.
    - Original 3/4-inch Video-cassette, undated (Box 15, Video-cassette UA.22.02.0001-Umatic-0139)
      2 Duke 8 - Sasakawa; duke Openting with Musk; Sasakawa Opening
    - Transcript and clippings, 1979-1982 (Box 27)
  - Schlesinger, James, 1987; 56
    - Original 3/4-inch Video-cassette, 1987 February 24 (Box 12, Video-cassette UA.22.02.0001-Umatic-0093)
      President's Guest House; Duke University; Interview Panel: Ole R. Holsti, Richard A. Stubbing, A. Kenneth Pye; Camera I Tape 1; Shot: Wide Angle; Audio Channels 1 & 2 mono; no time code; Directed by: Eric Leary
    - Original 3/4-inch Video-cassette, 1987 February 24 (Box 12, Video-cassette UA.22.02.0001-Umatic-0094)
      President's Guest House; Duke University; Interview Panel: Ole R. Holsti, Richard A. Stubbing, A. Kenneth Pye; Camera I Tape 2; Shot: Wide Angle; Audio Channels 1 & 2 mono; no time code; Directed by: Eric Leary
    - Original 3/4-inch Video-cassette, 1987 February 24 (Box 13, Video-cassette UA.22.02.0001-Umatic-0095)
      President's Guest House; Duke University; Interview Panel: Ole R. Holsti, Richard A. Stubbing, A. Kenneth Pye; Camera II Tape 1; Shot: CU Shlesinger; Audio Channels 1 & 2 mono; no time code; Directed by: Eric Leary
    - Original 3/4-inch Video-cassette, 1987 February 24 (Box 13, Video-cassette UA.22.02.0001-Umatic-0096)
      President's Guest House; Duke University; Interview Panel: Ole R. Holsti, Richard A. Stubbing, A. Kenneth Pye; Camera II Tape 2; Shot: CU Shlesinger; Audio Channels 1 & 2 mono; no time code; Directed by: Eric Leary
    - Original 3/4-inch Video-cassette, 1987 February 24 (Box 13, Video-cassette UA.22.02.0001-Umatic-0097)
      President's Guest House; Duke University; Interview Panel: Ole R. Holsti, Richard A. Stubbing, A. Kenneth Pye; Camera II Tape 3; Shot: CU Shlesinger; Audio Channels 1 & 2 mono; no time code; Directed by: Eric Leary
    - Original 3/4-inch Video-cassette, 1987 February 23 (Box 13, Video-cassette UA.22.02.0001-Umatic-0098)
      James Schlesinger -- 86/87 Rutherford Lecturer; February 23, 1987, Camera Original -- Tape 1
    - Original 3/4-inch Video-cassette, 1987 February 23 (Box 13, Video-cassette UA.22.02.0001-Umatic-0099)
      James Schlesinger -- 86/87 Rutherford Lecturer; February 23, 1987, Camera Original -- Tape 2
    - Original 3/4-inch Video-cassette, 1987 February 23 (Box 13, Video-cassette UA.22.02.0001-Umatic-0100)
      James Schlesinger -- 86/87 Rutherford Lecturer; February 23, 1987, Camera Original -- Tape 3
    - Original 3/4-inch Video-cassette, 1987 February 24 (Box 13, Video-cassette UA.22.02.0001-Umatic-0101)
      President's Guest House; Duke University; Interview Panel: Ole R. Holsti, Timothy Lomperis, Richard Stubbing; Camera I Tape 3; Shot: Wide Angle; Audio Channels 1 & 2 mono; no time code; Directed by: Eric Leary
    - Original 3/4-inch Video-cassette, 1987 February 24 (Box 13, Video-cassette UA.22.02.0001-Umatic-0102)
      President's Guest House; Duke University; Interview Panel: Ole R. Holsti, James David Barber, Timothy Lamperis; Camera I Tape 4; Shot: Wide Angle; Audio Channels 1 & 2 mono; no time code; Directed by: Eric Leary
    - Original 3/4-inch Video-cassette, 1987 February 24 (Box 13, Video-cassette UA.22.02.0001-Umatic-0103)
      President's Guest House; Duke University; Interview Panel: Ole R. Holsti, James David Barber, Timoth Lomperis; Camera II Tape 4; Shot: CU Shlesinger; Audio Channels 1 & 2 mono; no time code; Directed by: Eric Leary
    - Original 3/4-inch Video-cassette, 1987 February 23 & 24 (Box 13, Video-cassette UA.22.02.0001-Umatic-0104)
      Edit Master w/TC -- Tape 1
    - Original 3/4-inch Video-cassette, 1987 February 23 & 24 (Box 13, Video-cassette UA.22.02.0001-Umatic-0105)
      Edit Master w/TC -- Tape 2